[Music]
[音乐]
good afternoon welcome my name is Stuart
下午好，我叫斯图尔特
marks I work at Oracle in the Java
标志着我在Java中使用Oracle
platform group work on Java the open JDK
Java平台小组工作的开放式JDK
in the core libraries area so today's
在核心图书馆领域，所以今天
talk is optional the mother of all bike
谈话是可选的，所有自行车的母亲
sheds I'm going to be spending an entire
棚子，我要花整整
technical session talking about a single
技术会议谈论一个
API and talk about why we need it how to
API并讨论为什么我们需要它
use it how to misuse or abuse it to talk
用它来滥用或滥用它说话
a little bit about this notion of bike
关于自行车的一些概念
shedding which I talked about in the
我在
title and then wrap it up all right
标题，然后将其包装好
why do we need optional so let's talk
为什么我们需要可选的，所以让我们谈谈
about what an API looks like without
没有API的情况
optional so before Java 8 it was pretty
可选，因此在Java 8之前很漂亮
common to have an API that looked for
常见的具有寻找的API
something and there's a possibility that
某事，并且有可能
that API might not find what it was
该API可能找不到它是什么
looking for so let's let's describe this
寻找，让我们来描述一下
using an example an early in fact this
举个例子，其实这很早
was actually a real example because this
实际上是一个真实的例子，因为
is one of the one of the api's we had in
是我们拥有的api之一
the streams API in an early draft of it
流API的早期草稿
we had something I'll call search that
我们有一个我称之为搜索的东西
took a predicate and if it found
拿了一个谓词，如果发现
something in a stream that matched that
流中与之匹配的东西
predicate it would return it great
断言它将返回伟大
well what if it doesn't find anything
好吧，如果什么都找不到
that matches the predicate well I mean
符合谓词的意思
what do you do return null I mean you
你是怎么返回null我的意思是你
you that's what you always do with Java
这就是您一直使用Java所做的事情
you return null so that's that was the
您返回null，那就是
early draft API of this method in stream
流中此方法的早期API
so the example here is I have a
所以这里的例子是我有一个
predicate which checks the ID of a
谓词检查一个ID
customer so I write a method that
客户，所以我写了一个方法
searches a list of customers looking for
搜索正在寻找的客户列表
a customer with that ID and then it
具有该ID的客户，然后
returns the matching customer or it
返回匹配的客户或它
returns null ok seems simple enough all
返回null，确定似乎很简单
right so now let's say I want to return
对了，现在让我们说我想回来
the customers name whose matches that
与之匹配的客户名称
idea that ID ok so we have a nice stream
想法ID好，所以我们有一个很好的流
here we we call our search method on it
在这里，我们称其为搜索方法
and pass a predicate that matches the
并传递与
customer ID get its name and return that
客户ID获取其名称并返回
well that that looks like it does the
好吧，看起来像
right thing except in the case where
正确的事情，除非
search returns null that will throw a
搜索返回null，这将引发
nullpointerexception
空指针异常
this probably happens all the time so
这可能一直在发生，所以
what do you need to do okay
你需要做什么
first run your stream and store the
首先运行您的流并存储
results in a local variable and then do
产生局部变量，然后执行
a check in that local variable against
检查该局部变量
null and if it's not null then you go
null，如果不为null，则转到
ahead and call get name but if it is no
提前打电话给名字，如果不是
then you have to do something else in
那么你必须做其他事情
this case we're just going to return
在这种情况下，我们将要返回
some placeholder string and this works
一些占位符字符串，这有效
this is fine and I think we have to do
这很好，我认为我们必须做
this all the time but this is kind of
一直这样，但这有点
cluttered the first thing is it's easy
凌乱的第一件事就是很容易
to make this mistake and forget to check
犯这个错误而忘记检查
for a null the second thing is when you
零，第二件事是当你
do add the check for null it adds a
确实添加了null检查，它添加了一个
bunch of clutter to your code alright so
一堆混乱的代码好吧
in Java 8 we said okay I think we can do
在Java 8中，我们说可以，我认为我们可以做到
better with this with this kind of
这种更好的与此
problem and so we introduced the new API
问题，因此我们引入了新的API
called
叫
optional it's a generic type has a type
可选，它是通用类型，具有类型
T and it can be an instance of optional
T，它可以是可选的实例
can be in one of two states it can
可以处于两种状态之一
either be empty or it can contain a non
可以为空，也可以包含非
null reference to an object of type T so
空引用类型为T的对象，因此
if it does contain a nominal reference
如果确实包含名义参考
we call that present or the optional has
我们称该礼物或可选礼物具有
a value present and if there isn't a
存在一个值，如果没有
reference of type P in there we say that
那里的类​​型P的引用我们说
it is empty occasionally I hear people
有时候我是空的
say that it contains null and maybe
说它包含空值，也许
that's true in the implementation but I
在实现中是正确的，但我
think there's a very confusing way to
认为有一种非常混乱的方法
think about it because an optional the
考虑一下，因为一个可选的
idea of optional is to think about
可选的想法是考虑
presence or absence of something
有无东西
distinctly from null references or not
是否与空引用明显不同
so in fact I think it's it's it's a
所以实际上我认为这是
sloppy terminology to say that an
马虎的术语说
optional contains null so we say an
可选包含null，因此我们说
optional is present or it is absent or
可选存在或不存在或
value is present or absent in and
和中存在或不存在值
optional there are few specializations
可选，专业很少
off for primitive values optional inch
为原始值关闭，可选英寸
long and double not going to cover those
长而双倍不会覆盖那些
but they're they're mostly parallel to
但他们是他们基本上平行于
the optional that can contain reference
可以包含参考的可选
now optional is an ordinary class and
现在可选是普通类，并且
like everything in Java every class and
就像Java每个类中的所有内容，
have references to instance you
引用了您的实例
census and those references can be null
人口普查，这些参考可以为空
never ever ever use null as a reference
永远不会使用null作为参考
for an optional itself now if you use
如果您现在使用可选的本身
stylized uses of optional the way I'm
我使用可选方式的风格化使用
going to talk about in this talk
在这个演讲中要谈论
it basically is not a problem just
基本上这不是问题
remember don't use null when you have an
请记住，当您有一个
optional so what I'm going to do here is
可选的，所以我在这里要做的是
as I go along and going to be
当我继续前进并将成为
introducing a set of rules for what I
为我介绍一套规则
think are proper use of optional so
认为适当使用可选的所以
here's rule number one never ever use
这是永远不会使用的规则第一
null for an optional variable or return
null为可选变量或返回
value and I'll present these at the end
价值，我将在最后介绍这些
so you don't have to worry about
所以你不用担心
capturing them all alright so the
很好地捕获它们，所以
rationale for optional provides a
可选的理由提供了
limited mechanism meaning it's we're not
有限的机制意味着我们不是
intending to solve every last problem in
打算解决所有的最后一个问题
the universe to limited mechanism for
宇宙有限机制
method return types I think that's a key
方法返回类型，我认为这是一个关键
point the focus of optional is on method
指出可选方法的重点是方法
return values and so it's also useful
返回值，所以它也很有用
where there's a clear need to represent
明显需要代表的地方
no results that's like a finding or
没有类似发现的结果或
searching example where I think it's
搜索我认为是的示例
quite legitimate to search for something
找东西很合法
and not have a result so you need a way
并没有结果，所以您需要一种方法
to represent that and we're returning
代表这一点，我们正在返回
null is likely to cause errors and so
null可能会导致错误，因此
you saw an example of that in the
您在其中看到了一个例子
examples a few slides ago where if
几张幻灯片的示例，如果
you're turned on you if you immediately
如果你马上就打开你
dereference it you get a null pointer
解引用它得到一个空指针
exception and it's it's tempting to do
例外，这很诱人
that in code it's easy it's convenient
在代码中很容易很方便
but it introduces null pointer
但它引入了空指针
exceptions so if you have that kind of
例外，所以如果你有那种
situation that's where optional can help
可选可以帮助的情况
you alright so let's go back to that
你还好，让我们回到那个
example and see if we can do better so
看看我们是否可以做得更好
instead of search what we ended up with
而不是搜索我们最终得到了什么
in the streams API was find find in E
在流API中找到在E中找到
and fine first and so what those do is
首先，所以这些是
return so if you have a stream of type T
返回，如果您有T类型的流
then find any or fine first we'll return
然后找到任何或好的我们将返回
an optional of type P and it's slightly
类型P的可选，它略带
different to you don't actually pass a
与你不同，实际上并没有通过
predicate directly to the find method
直接基于find方法
basically upstream of the find method
基本上在find方法的上游
you you fill you put in a filter
你填满你放入一个过滤器
operation so that's what we have here we
操作，这就是我们在这里拥有的
take our customer list stream it run it
带我们的客户列表流运行它
through a filter that looks for a
通过寻找一个
matching ID fine first we want to find
首先要找到匹配的ID
the first customer that matched
第一个匹配的客户
matching ID and then now we have we have
匹配的ID，然后我们有了
some representation of of a customer
客户的某种表示
that might or might not be there and we
那可能存在或可能不存在，我们
want to get its name so the example here
想获得它的名字，所以这里的例子
is that we want to get the name okay so
是我们要取好名字，所以
there's a problem here because fine
这里有一个问题，因为很好
first returns an optional but get name
首先返回一个可选但获取名称
is a method on customer so that doesn't
是对客户的一种方法，所以不会
work
工作
so we have to do something different all
所以我们必须做一些不同的事情
right so let's let's break this apart
对，所以让我们分开
here for the sake of example it gets
为了举例，在这里
better don't worry so let's take the
最好不要担心，让我们来
optional customer return value from fine
罚款的可选客户退货价值
first and store that in a local variable
首先并将其存储在本地变量中
so now we have an optional that might or
所以现在我们有一个可选的
might not contain a customer and we want
可能没有客户，我们想要
to get name on that somehow so so how do
以某种方式获得名称，所以怎么办
we do that there's there's a piece
我们这样做是有一块的
missing here all right there's a method
错过这里好吧，有一种方法
called get an optional that gets the
称为获取一个可选的
value that out of the optional great
重视那些可选的伟大
we're done oh well what about the empty
我们做完了哦，那空的呢
case right it's just like when we
正确的情况就像我们
couldn't find a customer that matched
找不到匹配的客户
that ID what gets returned an empty
该ID返回的内容为空
optional what happens when you call get
可选调用get时会发生什么
on auntie optional it throws no such
在可选的阿姨身上，没有抛出这样的东西
element exception okay well we haven't
元素异常好吧，我们还没有
bought anything here because it's just
在这里买了什么，因为
the same this is almost exactly the same
差不多这几乎完全一样
as what happens if you call call a
如您打电话给
method on an old reference you get some
在旧参考书上的方法，您会得到一些
exception thrown so we have bought any
抛出异常，所以我们买了任何
you know this hasn't bought us anything
你知道这还没给我们买什么
yet so we have to do we have to work
但是我们必须要做的是我们必须工作
harder to make this to make this work
很难做到这一点
right so that's what I'm going to tell
对，这就是我要说的
you how to how to use optional properly
你如何正确使用可选
so like you if you had a reference you
如果您有参考，就喜欢您
could test it to see whether it was an
可以测试一下，看看是否是
all or non null if you have an optional
全部或非null（如果有可选选项）
there's a method called is present
有一种方法叫做
that's boolean that tells you whether it
布尔值告诉您是否
has a value present or whether a value
是否有值或是否有值
is absent so here's a safe way to
缺席，所以这是一种安全的方法
implement our example we want to run our
实施我们的示例，我们要运行我们的
stream and get an optional customer as
串流并获得一个可选客户
the result so that's a so that might
结果是这样可能
contain a customer that matches or it
包含匹配的客户
might be empty and so we say if that
可能是空的，所以我们说如果
optional has a value present
可选值存在
and get the customer out of it and call
吸引顾客，并致电
get name on it and so that works because
得到它的名字，所以行得通，因为
since the optional has a value present
因为可选值存在一个值
we know get will return that reference
我们知道get将返回该引用
and that's non null otherwise we return
那不是非null否则我们返回
some default value and here I'm just
一些默认值，这里我只是
using the string unknown okay but again
使用字符串未知好吗，但再次
this is this is kind of same as testing
这和测试是一样的
for null versus non null but actually
对于null与非null，但实际上
it's a little bit better because instead
会好一点，因为
of accidentally calling methods on a non
非
null reference what optional does is it
空引用是可选的
kind of forces you to say oh I have an
你要说的是一种力量
optional here that means it might be
在这里是可选的，这意味着它可能是
empty how do I handle this case but
空我该如何处理这种情况，但
still the code is not very good because
仍然代码不是很好，因为
we have to have a local variable and we
我们必须有一个局部变量，我们
have to do this explicit test in here oh
必须在这里做这个明确的测试哦
but before I move on here's rule number
但在我继续之前，这里是规则编号
two never use optional dot get unless
两个从不使用可选的点获取，除非
you can prove that the optional you're
你可以证明你是可选的
calling it on has a value present right
调用它具有当前值
so if you call get on an empty optional
所以如果你打电话给一个空的可选
it throws no such element exception and
它不会抛出此类元素异常，并且
that's that's the kind of equivalent of
那就是相当于
a null pointer exception so you could
空指针异常，因此您可以
write all your code this way and say if
用这种方式编写所有代码，然后说
if it is present or use a ternary
如果存在或使用三元
operator or whatever essentially saying
运算符或本质上在说什么
if it is present then get else do
如果存在，则另做
something else and you know that's okay
还有别的，你知道那没关系
but but we we can do better and so
但是我们可以做得更好等等
anyway
无论如何
we should we can't we can do better and
我们应该不能做得更好，
we should do better so rule number three
我们应该做得更好，所以第三条规则
is don't fall into the trap of always
不要陷入永远的陷阱
using use present and get instead use
使用use present并获取代替使用
the techniques I'm going to show you in
我将向您展示的技术
subsequent slides they're a bunch of
随后的幻灯片，他们是一堆
alternatives to using is present and get
存在和使用替代方法
alright so there's all family of methods
好了，所以有各种各样的方法
on optional called or else and so I'm
在可选称为否则，所以我
just going to either quick little
只是快一点
examples here but the basic premise is
这里的例子，但基本前提是
if the optional has a value present that
如果可选值存在，则表明
value is simply returned or else
只是返回值，否则
something different happens and so there
发生了一些不同的事情，所以那里
are three methods here the first one
这是三种方法第一种
or else we'll return a default value or
否则我们将返回默认值或
else get instead of returning a default
否则获取而不是返回默认值
value it will call a supplier which is
价值它将呼叫供应商
like a lambda expression or method
像lambda表达式或方法
reference you can provide but it will
您可以提供参考，但它将
call a supplier to create or obtain that
致电供应商以创建或获取
default value that's then returned and
然后返回的默认值
or else throw will say oh okay this
否则扔会说哦，好吧
should never be this net this should
不应该是这个网，应该是
never be empty so throw an exception and
永远不会为空，所以抛出异常，
what it does is it allows you to throw
它的作用是让您扔
an exception of of a chosen type so for
所选类型的例外，因此
instance it might you might want illegal
例如，您可能想违法
State exception instead of no such
国家例外，而不是没有
element exception but again the the
元素异常，但再次
thing that's it's a little odd about the
事情有点奇怪
naming here in isolation at least is or
至少在这里单独命名是或
else extract the value if present and it
否则提取该值（如果存在）
always does that and then or else or
总是这样做，然后否则
else get and or else throw will do
否则得到，否则将抛出
different things if the value is absent
如果缺少该值则不同
all right so there's another method
好的，所以还有另一种方法
that's extremely useful which is math
这是非常有用的，这是数学
and it's math in a sense of transform
从某种意义上讲它是数学
kind of the same the same kind of usage
相同的用法
as the math on the stream on stream
作为流上的数学
object so what map does is okay so now
对象，所以地图的作用就可以了
this is a recapitulation of our example
这是我们例子的概括
here and I'll just show you code that
在这里，我将向您展示代码
uses a map so what map does is it says
使用地图，所以地图会说
if there's a value present it calls the
如果存在值，则调用
mapper function on it and takes the
映射器功能，并采取
result of that and puts it back into an
结果，并将其放回
optional but if the optional empty it
可选，但如果可选为空，则为空
just does nothing and passes through the
只是什么都不做，并通过
empty sort of okay that's kind of a
空的好吧，有点像
mouthful but that's exactly what we want
满嘴，但这正是我们想要的
to do here so in our stream example we
为此，在我们的流示例中，
got we did search for a customer with a
我们确实找到了一个具有
matching ID and we got an optional of
匹配的ID，我们可以选择
customer and what we really wanted the
客户以及我们真正想要的
name and so we call math with the
名称，所以我们用
getname method with a meth with a
带有meth的meth的getname方法
reference to the customer get name
引用客户的名字
method what that does is if there's a
方法是什么，如果有
customer in there and replaces it with
客户在那里，并替换为
the customers name so now we have an
客户的名字，所以现在我们有一个
optional string but if there was no
可选字符串，但如果没有
customer in there
客户在那里
it's an empty optional now what we do is
这是一个空的可选内容，我们要做的是
we chain or else on to the end of it and
我们将其链结，否则将其结束
so if that customer was present it was
所以如果那个顾客在场
replaced with the name and then or else
用名称替换，然后否则
remember the first thing that or else
记住第一件事
does is extract the value that's in
所做的是提取其中的值
there so if we bought the customer we
在那里，如果我们买了客户，我们
changed we mapped it into the customers
改变了我们将其映射到客户中
name and then that's what we returned
名称，然后这就是我们返回的内容
but if the optional was empty the mapper
但是如果可选为空，则映射器
function is just ignored and or else
函数只是被忽略，否则
says return unknown which is our default
说返回未知，这是我们的默认值
value so you can start to see okay we
值，所以您可以开始看到好吧，我们
chained these methods up on optional in
将这些方法链接到可选的
in an interesting way and we can we can
以一种有趣的方式，我们可以
get some really convenient behaviors
得到一些非常方便的行为
here but it gets better because we don't
在这里，但是会变得更好，因为我们不
need that pesky local variable anymore
不再需要那个讨厌的局部变量
we can chain these methods right off the
我们可以直接将这些方法链接起来
end of the stream so now we have we have
流的尽头，所以现在我们有了
a stream that terminates with fine first
流先终止的流
but we can keep chaining methods on it
但是我们可以保留链接方法
so fine first returns an optional and
所以很好先返回一个可选的
then we just call mapper on it to
然后我们就可以调用mapper
transform the value that might be
转换可能是
present in the optional or else we
存在于可选的，否则我们
return some default value so that makes
返回一些默认值，使
that makes things a lot more convenient
这使事情变得更加方便
and neater so you lose the need for
整洁，所以您不需要
local variables and you lose the need
局部变量，您就失去了需要
for explicitly testing conditions all
用于明确测试所有条件
right so there are few other methods I
对，所以我没有其他方法
want to run through pretty quickly on
想要很快通过
optional one is the filter method and so
可选方法之一是过滤方法，因此
what filter does is it establishes an
过滤器的作用是建立一个
invariant over what value might be
在什么值上不变
present in the optional and if something
存在于可选的，如果有的话
doesn't meet that invariant then it
不满足那个不变性
returns an empty optional so here we
返回一个空的可选值，所以在这里我们
have an example that really came from an
有一个例子真的来自
early access version of JDK 9 I think
我认为JDK 9的早期访问版本
I've heard that this code has been been
我听说这段代码已经
edited beyond recognition so you won't
编辑得面目全非，所以您不会
it won't be in there if you go looking
如果你去找它就不会在那里
for it now but basically you know it's
现在就可以了，但是基本上你知道
this stuff about modules and layers and
关于模块和层的东西
configurations and stuff the exact the
配置和确切的东西
exact case is not that important but the
确切的情况不是那么重要，但是
invariant is what's interesting here
不变的是这里有趣的是
which is we have a config and we want to
这是我们有一个配置，我们想
make sure that it has a parent and its
确保它有一个父母及其
parent is the same as our parent and so
父母和我们父母一样
that's what this code here does this is
这就是这段代码所做的
kind of a conventional usage of optional
一种可选的常规用法
like I was saying before it doesn't kind
就像我之前说过的那样
of kind of the conventional thing with
与传统的东西
is present and get and if that condition
存在并获得，如果这种情况
and and really this is checking the
而且实际上这是检查
opposite of the condition that they want
他们想要的条件相反
to to assert and so if the opposite is
要断言，所以如果相反
true then then it throws an illegal
如果是真的，那么它会抛出非法
argument exception and so a better way
参数异常以及更好的方法
to rewrite this code is like this so
重写这段代码就像这样
what we want to do is we write a filter
我们想要做的是编写一个过滤器
and that takes a predicate that says
这需要一个谓词
okay we we have a config and we get its
好吧，我们有一个配置，我们得到了它
parent and we want that parent to be
父母，我们希望那个父母成为
present and be equal to our config and
当前并等于我们的配置
so what what you get at the end of that
那末你会得到什么
is an optional that contains a value
是包含值的可选
that meets the predicate otherwise it's
符合谓词，否则
empty and in this case if it's empty
空，在这种情况下，如果为空
that's what's illegal so we say or else
那是非法的，所以我们说不然
throw illegal argument exception and so
抛出非法的参数异常等等
you notice how this this reads a lot
你会注意到这读得很多
nicer than that that if statement which
比那个if语句更好
had complicated boolean expressions and
具有复杂的布尔表达式，并且
negations we get the parent we assert
否定我们得到我们断言的父母
that it's configuration is equal to this
它的配置等于这个
configuration or else throw an exception
配置，否则抛出异常
alright so there's another method called
好了，还有另一种方法
if present and it's pretty confusing
如果存在，这很令人困惑
because there's there I already talked
因为那里我已经说过了
about a method called he is present and
关于一种叫他存在的方法
so this one is if present and it's a
因此，如果存在，这是一个
little little too easy to get these
一点点太容易获得这些
mixed up so sorry about that but here's
对此感到很抱歉，但这是
an example from another example from the
来自另一个例子的例子
JDK of where we can use this so so what
JDK我们可以在哪里使用它
if present does is it executes a lambda
如果存在，则执行lambda
expression if the optional has a value
表达式（如果可选）具有值
present and so the use case here this is
目前，所以这里的用例是
kind of the original code which is sort
原始代码的种类
of written out so we got a task from
写下来，所以我们得到了一个任务
somewhere that might or might not have a
某个地方可能有或没有
task so it returns an optional task so
任务，因此它返回一个可选任务，因此
the conventional code is okay tests are
常规代码是可以的，测试是
optional to see if it has a value
可选的，看它是否有一个值
present if it does we get the task out
如果有的话，我们就把任务拿出来
of it and then ask an executor to run
然后请执行者运行
that task pretty conventional but we can
这个任务很常规，但是我们可以
use the if present method to make that
使用if present方法
much nicer
好多了
I could say get tasks which returns the
我可以说得到任务返回
optional now notice we don't have to
现在可选，请注意，我们不必
store this in a local variable we'll
将其存储在本地变量中
just chain chain off of that we say if
只是说，我们说如果
present and then has a lambda expression
现在，然后有一个lambda表达式
that submits the task to the executor
将任务提交给执行者
okay and we can do a little bit better
好吧，我们可以做得更好
because I like method references so we
因为我喜欢方法引用，所以我们
could say get task if present
可以说获得任务（如果存在）
hey executor run that task and we're
嘿执行者执行该任务，我们
done so that makes things much neater
这样做使事情变得更加整洁
alright there are even more methods on
好吧，还有更多的方法
optional a couple static factor methods
可选的几种静态因子方法
and this is this is where you get
这就是你得到的
optional instances from in the first
从第一个开始的可选实例
place there are no public instructors on
地方没有公共教练
optional so if you want an empty
可选的，所以如果您想清空
optional you just call optional dot
可选，您只需调用可选点
empty and if you want an optional that
空，如果您想要一个可选的
contains a value you say optional dot of
包含您说的可选点的值
and a crucial point here is that if you
关键一点是，如果您
pass a reference to type T that
传递对类型T的引用
reference must be non null so you can
引用必须为非null，以便您可以
never store a null reference in an
永远不要在
optional there's equal to hash code
可选，等于哈希码
which do pretty much what you expect and
几乎可以达到您的期望
and it's like you know so what who cares
就像你知道，谁在乎
well it turns out that this is really
事实证明，这确实是
useful in unit testing so if you have a
在单元测试中很有用，所以如果您有
unit test for a method that returns an
单元测试返回的方法
optional here's how to here's how to
可选这里是如何这里是如何
test fit you say assert equals optional
您说断言等于可选的测试拟合
dot of expected value or certain equals
期望值或某些等于的点
optional not empty I think this is the J
可选不为空，我认为这是J
unit style where the expected value is
期望值为的单元样式
on the left in anyway so so equals works
无论如何在左边，所以等于作品
as you expect and in fact compares the
如您所料，实际上是
things inside the optionals if they are
可选内容中的内容（如果有）
both present alright so there are some
都很好，所以有一些
new methods we're adding two optional in
新方法，我们在其中添加了两个可选
java nine there's there's the there's a
Java 9那里有一个
method that converts an optional into a
将可选内容转换为
stream consisting of zero or one
由零或一组成的流
elements and then there are couple
元素，然后有几个
additional utilities there's if present
如果存在其他实用程序
or else which is kind of a mouthful and
否则这是一口
there's optional dot or and i'm not
有可选的点或我不
going to go into these in detail I think
我想详细介绍这些
the use cases are a little more complex
用例比较复杂
than I have time for today but they do
比我今天有时间但他们确实
come up
上来
menu and again the usual case of you
菜单，又是你平常的情况
know you have a stream that wants to
知道你有一个流想要
find something and you need to handle
找到东西，你需要处理
the case where it might be present or
可能存在的情况或
absent and sometimes you need to do
缺席，有时您需要做
something with with you need to do
和你在一起需要做的事情
something with both the need to take
既需要服用的东西
action on both the present case and the
对本案和本案的诉讼
absent case and sometimes you also want
缺席的情况下，有时您还想要
to combine two optional values in a
合并两个可选值
particular way so that's what optional
特殊的方式，所以这是可选的
or does all right so here's an example
还是可以，所以这是一个例子
of using optional dot stream
使用可选点流的过程
Smoove we had a list of customer IDs and
消除我们的客户ID列表，
you wanted to transform that into a list
您想将其转换为列表
of customers right so you run that
正确的客户群，因此您可以
through stream and you map that to
通过流，您将其映射到
customer find by ID so now you have a
客户通过ID查找，因此现在您有了一个
list of customer you have a list of
客户清单，您有一个清单
optional customers some of which might
可选客户，其中一些可能
be empty so you have a bunch of empty
是空的，所以你有一堆空的
optionals inside your list so that's not
列表中的可选内容，因此不是
very good
很好
so let's filter that on optionals that
所以让我们在可选的
are present and then map that to
存在，然后将其映射到
optional dot get to get the actual
可选点获取实际值
customers out of the of the optional and
客户中的可选和
that works in Java and it's a little
它可以在Java中工作，而且有点
nicer because we can run that through
更好，因为我们可以通过
flat map and the result of flat map in
平面图和中的平面图结果
the stream so we can compress those two
流，所以我们可以压缩这两个
operations down to one so we can say if
操作降到一，所以我们可以说
we have we have a stream of optionals we
我们有一些可选的东西，我们
can flat map those and it just drops out
可以将那些平面地图绘制出来
the just drops out the empty optionals
只是放弃了空的可选
I'll take questions at the end thing
最后我会提问
excuse me I'll take questions at the end
对不起，我会在最后提问
okay now so there's there's another
好吧，现在有另外一个
important use case which is how to adapt
重要的用例是如何适应
if you're writing new code you're using
如果您正在编写新代码，则使用的是
optional that's great how to adapt that
可选的，很好的适应
code to other parts of your code that
编码到代码的其他部分
might still be using nullable references
可能仍在使用可为空的引用
so we have a couple of techniques for
所以我们有两种技术
for dealing with those so if you suppose
与这些人打交道，如果你想
from let's say from my point of view I'm
从我的角度说
working on code that uses optional and
处理使用可选和
I'm calling into some code that might
我正在调用一些可能会
return a null so how do I deal with how
返回null，那么我该如何处理
do I deal with nulls how do I bring
我应该如何处理空值
nulls into the optional world so there's
null进入可选世界，所以有
a different static factory method called
一种不同的静态工厂方法，称为
optional dot of nullable
可为空的可选点
and that allows the reference to be null
并且允许引用为空
and so here's the key thing it doesn't
所以这是关键的事情
store a null reference as the value in
将空引用存储为值
an optional so again there's no way to
可选的，所以再次没有办法
have an optional present that has a null
有一个空的礼物
reference so if you pass optional of
参考，所以如果您通过可选的
nullable unknown reference you get an
可为空的未知参考，您将获得
empty optional I think this throws
空可选，我认为这会抛出
people a little bit but I think it
人们有点，但我认为
actually makes things simpler because
实际上使事情变得更简单，因为
again there are only two cases see if
同样只有两种情况
you did have an optional that could
你确实有一个可以
contain a null reference you might you
包含一个空引用，您可能会
might say oh it's present get the thing
可能会说，哦，现在有东西
out of it and then still end up with a
从中出来，然后仍然以
null reference which kind of gets you
空引用哪种会让您受益
all the way back to the beginning of the
一直回到开始
talk you have to test for null again so
谈谈您必须再次测试null
we don't allow null references to be in
我们不允许在空引用
optionals and so optional of nullable
可选，因此为nullable的可选
with a null returns an empty optional
如果为null，则返回一个空的可选
okay so now you want to go another way I
好吧，现在你想走另一条路
have an optional that might might be
有一个可能是
present or absent and then I want to
在场或不在场，然后我想
pass it to some code that's expecting a
将其传递给期望
nullable reference how do I do that well
可为空的引用我该怎么做
it turns out if you just say or else
事实证明，如果你只是说否则
null it does exactly the right thing it
null，它做正确的事
converts it extracts the value if it's
转换它提取值，如果它是
present but if it if it's an empty
存在，但如果为空
optional it just turns it into null so
可选的，它只是将其变为null，所以
something needs a knowable reference
某些东西需要一个熟悉的参考
just call or else Mel on your optional
只是打电话，否则梅尔就可以了
and I think this is the or else knows
我认为这是其他
sometimes overused I think that the main
有时我认为主要
use case where you should focus on is if
您应该关注的用例是
you're calling into code or you need to
您正在调用代码，或者您需要
pass pass a value to something that is
通过将值传递给
expecting an honorable reference that's
期望得到一个光荣的参考
the time to use it otherwise sometimes
有时使用它的时间
people really well people people overuse
人们真的很好人们过度使用
tough
强硬
all right that's my quick rundown on
好的，那是我的快速失败
proper uses of optional and so there's a
正确使用可选的，所以有一个
lot of people who kind of grab onto
很多人抓住
optional say oh look at all the cool
可选说哦，看看所有酷
things we can do with it and so there's
我们可以用它做的事情，所以有
there's use misuse abstruse use and
有滥用，滥用，滥用
abuse in all kinds of ways that i think
我认为以各种方式滥用
that optional should not be used so I'll
该可选选项不应该使用，所以我会
run through a few quick examples of that
通过几个简单的例子
all right so one thing that people do is
好吧，人们要做的一件事是
they say hmm oh it's really cool you can
他们说嗯，真的很酷，你可以
change methods and you no longer have to
改变方法，您不再需要
write if statements so suppose I have a
写if语句，以为我有一个
method called process that takes a
称为process的方法
nullable string well I could just do the
可以为空的字符串，我可以做
simple thing and test that against null
简单的事情，并针对null进行测试
or I could say I'll create an optional
或者我可以说我会创建一个可选的
of knowable and then call or else get on
知道的，然后打电话，否则继续
it and have it call something else so
它并让它调用其他东西
why bother just test it against null
为什么只需要对null进行测试
everybody understands what testing
每个人都了解什么测试
against null means and so if you have
反对空手段，所以如果你有
something if you have a reference that's
如果您有一个参考是
knowable just tested and null usually
已知刚刚测试过，通常为null
creating an optional just for the sake
为了方便而创建一个可选的
of changing methods off of it and then
改变方法，然后
extracting the value at the end doesn't
最后提取值不会
buy you anything so here we have rule
给你买东西，所以我们有规则
number four generally bad idea to create
要创造的第四大坏主意
an optional for the express purpose of
用于明确目的的可选
chaining methods and then extracting it
链接方法，然后将其提取
and so I think the the anti-pattern
所以我认为反模式
there I see is when when you use
我看到的是当您使用时
optional entirely within a single method
完全在一个方法中可选
or even in a single statement again the
甚至再一次发表声明
main use case for optional is when
可选的主要用例是何时
you're returning a value to somebody and
您正在将价值返回给某人，
in the return position that value might
在返回位置，该值可能
or might not be present all right so
或可能不存在，所以
there's there more ways to avoid this
还有更多的方法可以避免这种情况
statement so this is a weird use case
声明，所以这是一个奇怪的用例
that somebody asked on Stack Overflow he
有人在Stack Overflow上问他
he has two optional big decimal values
他有两个可选的大十进制值
and he wants to add them together now
他想现在把它们加在一起
since they're optionals there's this
因为它们是可选的，所以有这个
question of what you do if one of those
问题，如果其中之一，你会怎么做
big decimal values is absent and you had
没有大的十进制值
kind of a strange rule which is if one
有点奇怪的规则
is present but the other is absent then
存在但另一个不存在
the absent one should be considered zero
缺席者应视为零
okay on the other hand if they're both
另一方面，如果他们都
absent then return and empty optional so
缺席，然后返回并清空可选内容，因此
so that's a little strange
所以有点奇怪
but that was his use case I'm not going
但这是他的用例，我不会
to say whether that's right or wrong so
说是对是错
somebody came up with an answer which is
有人想出了一个答案
oh I know
哦，我知道
let's stream the optionals and then
让我们流式传输可选内容，然后
filter and then map and then reduce them
过滤，然后映射，然后减少它们
it's like okay wait what does this do
就像这样，等一下
again and you really have to understand
再一次，你真的必须了解
the API as well in order to figure this
API也是如此
out I mean it's not the right thing and
出来，我的意思是这不是正确的事情，
in fact when I was going through the
事实上，当我正在经历
slides earlier I said wait a minute
我刚才说幻灯片稍等一下
there's a mistake here oh oh wait no
这里有一个错误哦哦等不
actually that is right all right so it's
其实没错，所以
it's really hard to understand and as
真的很难理解
well as I understand the the Java eight
我了解Java 8
stream API is and stuff I still stumble
流API是，我仍然迷迷糊糊
over this what it relies on is the
在此之上，它所依赖的是
single argument the single argument form
单参数单参数形式
of the reduce method actually returns an
的reduce方法实际上返回了
optional of what it found what what the
发现什么是可选的
results of the reduction anyway so I'm
无论如何减少的结果，所以我
not going to go through all the cases
不会经历所有情况
here it's too complicated and it's like
这里太复杂了，就像
wow this is clever it allowed you to
哇，这很聪明，它使您能够
avoid writing in this statement but you
避免在这句话中写，但是你
know when somebody writes clever code
知道有人写聪明的代码
it's it's it's one of these things
这是这些事情之一
that's that's that's too clever alright
那就是那太聪明了
so here's another answer and so what
所以这是另一个答案，那又怎样
happens is people sometimes get into
有时候人们会进入
this code golfing thing when they say I
当他们说我时，这个代码打高尔夫
can solve your problem in the fewest
可以在最少的时间内解决您的问题
number of characters and so here he says
字符数，所以他在这里说
oh let's map the optional and then in
哦，让我们映射可选的，然后在
the in the mapper function let's map the
在mapper函数中，让我们映射
second optional and then chain a few
第二个可选的，然后链接一些
methods on to that extracted map again
再次在提取的地图上使用方法
and then say or else the second one and
然后说第二个
it's like wow in order to understand
就像哇为了了解
this I actually had to pull out a sheet
我实际上不得不掏出一张纸
of paper and write out all the cases
并写出所有案例
this guy this guy's really clever
这个家伙，这个家伙真的很聪明
but you know I encourage you if you want
但是你知道我鼓励你
to if you want to figure out what this
如果你想弄清楚这是什么
does do the same thing I mean if you can
确实可以做到相同的意思
do it in your head
在你的头上做
great I can't a lot of piece of paper
太好了，我不能做很多纸
and run through all the cases of two
并经历了两种情况
inputs being empty or present or absent
输入为空或存在或不存在
or present and verify that you get the
或出示并确认您获得了
right result according to according to
根据的正确结果
the problem statement here I pretty much
我在这里的问题陈述
believe it's correct but boy this card
相信这是正确的，但是男孩这张卡
is this code hard to understand so
这段代码难理解吗？
here's the way I would write it and it's
这是我写的方式，这是
not the prettiest code but it kind of
不是最漂亮的代码，但是
says exactly what what the issue is if
说出问题到底是什么
neither is present return optional empty
都不存在返回可选的空
otherwise
除此以外
add some together substituting zero if
如果加零则加一些
one of the optionals is empty so to me
可选项目之一为空，所以对我来说
that reads much nicer and it's easier to
读起来更好，而且更容易
understand but it did lead me to rule
明白，但这确实使我统治
number five it's an optional chain is
五是可选链
nested or you have an intern or
巢状或实习生或
intermediate result of optional optional
可选的中间结果
of T it's probably too complex so don't
可能太复杂了，所以不要
write code like that alright so there's
这样写代码，所以有
this actually this is thirteen a TN into
这实际上是十三个TN
the bike shading a little bit but
自行车的阴影有点
there's this problem with optional dot
可选点存在此问题
get and so and yell like along are asked
被问及如此大喊
Brian gets the Java Java language
Brian获得Java Java语言
architect in interview a couple years
建筑师在面试了几年
ago what he thought the biggest mistake
以前他认为最大的错误
he made with Java eight was and he said
他用Java 8做的是，他说
optional dot get and the problem is and
可选的点获取，问题是和
the way he termed it wasn't attractive
他所说的方式没有吸引力
it was an attractive nuisance and get is
这是一个令人讨厌的麻烦，得到的是
such an obvious thing to call on
如此明显的事情
optional yet it leads you down some some
可选，但它会导致您失败
pretty I mean it leads you into making
漂亮，我的意思是它引导您进入
choice I should say it misleads you into
选择，我应该说这会误导您
making poor choices so it's a lot less
做出错误的选择，所以要少得多
useful than then a really short name
比起一个简短的名字有用
like get would indicate you can forget
像获取将表明您可以忘记
to guard it right remember one of my
为了保护自己，记住我的一个
earlier rules is never call get unless
以前的规则永远不会调用get，除非
you can prove that the the that the
您可以证明
optional has a value present so that
可选的值存在，以便
leads in turn people who are aware of
反过来导致意识到的人
the problems with get writing code all
所有编写代码的问题
around is present and get but they're
周围存在并获得但它们存在
usually much better alternatives like
通常更好的替代品，例如
those nicer methods like map and or else
那些更好的方法，例如map和or
and filter that I talked about before so
和过滤器，我之前谈论过的
really using get kind of tends to lead
真正使用得到倾向于导致
you in the wrong direction and so what
你朝错误的方向前进
we would like to do is eventually
我们想做的最终是
replace get and there are some
替换获取并有一些
complaints about that we wanted to
关于我们想要的抱怨
deprecate get and it caused too many too
不赞成使用get，它导致太多
many warnings but so get is still there
许多警告，但仍然存在
in jdk nine we may take a swing at it
在九丹麦克朗，我们可能会摇摆
again in jdk ten but get is not really i
再次在十丹麦克朗，但得到不是真的我
mean yet it's such a fundamental thing
意思是这是一件很基本的事情
but really try to avoid using it as we
但实际上我们尽量避免使用它
can
能够
right there a bunch of places where
就在那里一堆地方
people use optional where they really
人们在真正的地方使用可选
and it's not you know it's I'll come out
不是你知道我会出来
and say they really shouldn't do that I
说他们真的不应该那样做
think there's there's a way to over use
认为有一种过度使用的方法
optional so one of the things people do
可选的，所以人们做的一件事
is they say well I have an object with a
他们说好吗我有一个带有
bunch of fields in it and some of those
一堆领域，其中一些
fields might or might not contain values
字段可能包含或可能不包含值
ah therefore I should use optional and
啊，所以我应该使用可选和
it turns out that there are much they're
事实证明，他们有很多
often much better ways to represent the
通常更好的方式来代表
absence of value if you're designing
如果您正在设计，则没有价值
some kind of data class often something
某种数据类通常是
like a null object pattern is is is a
就像一个空对象模式是
really good way to do that or you know
这样做的好方法，或者你知道
sometimes you you know what value are
有时候你知道什么是价值
you going to use so just fill in its
您将要使用，所以只需填写其
replacement value yes if it's absent or
替换值是，如果不存在或
or actually it's not so bad to have an
或者实际上，拥有一个
actual nullable field as a private field
实际可为空的字段作为私有字段
of an object because you can control
对象的原因，因为您可以控制
where all the uses of that field pretty
该字段的所有用途都很漂亮
easily when it when that reference goes
当引用变得容易时
outside of your class then that's the
在课外，那就是
time to start worrying about this is
是时候开始担心这个了
nullable do I want to tell all my
我想告诉我所有的东西
clients they have to check for null
客户必须检查是否为空
that's the time when you when you want
那是你想要的时候
to talk about using optional instead of
谈论使用可选而不是
using optional in your internal
在内部使用可选
representation so another thing people
代表，另一件事是人
do is they say optional oh one thing
难道他们说可选一件事
that Java doesn't have is optional
Java没有的是可选的
program option ulm ethic parameters so
程序选项ulm伦理参数
notice where there's a shuttle subtle
注意哪里有穿梭的微妙之处
shift here I want optional method
移到这里我想要可选方法
parameters therefore I'm going to use
参数，因此我将使用
optional well they're really talking
他们真的在说选择性的嘛
about different things so this notion of
关于不同的事情，所以这个概念
optional method parameters doesn't
可选方法参数不
actually exist in Java does exist in two
实际上存在于Java中，确实存在于两个
other languages but it's basically you
其他语言，但基本上是您
know the ability to provide or not
知道提供或不提供的能力
provide arguments to a method call
提供方法调用的参数
whereas the Java dot util dot capital
而Java点util点大写
optional is a class and so those don't
可选的是一个类，所以那些不是
really fit even though they have the
即使他们有
same name and so the reason you don't
同一个名字，所以你不这样做的原因
want to use Java util optional to try to
想要使用Java util可选来尝试
emulate optional method parameters is
模拟可选方法参数是
that it really
真的
garbages up your call sites so you can't
浪费您的呼叫站点，因此您无法
as a caller you can't leave out a
作为呼叫者，您不能忽略
parameter that's required instead what
需要的参数，而不是什么
you have to say is optional dot empty or
您必须说的是可选点为空或
if you actually want to fill something
如果你真的想填补一些东西
in there you have to say optional done
在那你必须说可选完成
of some value and that just adds a lot
有价值的东西，这增加了很多
of clutter to all your callers so it
杂乱无章的呼叫者
doesn't really fulfill this notion of
并没有真正实现
optional method parameters at all and
可选的方法参数
then there's another place where where I
然后在另一个地方
see optional misused sometimes which is
有时看到可选的滥用
has elements inside of a collection so
在集合中包含元素，因此
like a list of optional of customers or
例如可选客户列表或
something like that people store that
像这样的人存储
away somewhere and you know it's you
离开某个地方，你知道是你
know it's beyond the scope of this this
知道这超出了此范围
talk to talk about that but are you're
谈论谈论这个，但是你是
representing something it's like why are
代表某种原因
you it's just kind of a funny code smell
你这只是一种有趣的代码气味
why do you have a list that contains
为什么您有一个包含以下内容的列表
things that might or might not be
可能会或可能不会的事情
present why are the empty ones in there
现在为什么那里是空的
at all and if there are no empty ones
根本没有空的
why not just have a list of customers
为什么不仅仅拥有客户列表
that makes perfect sense
完全有道理
so usually when there's optionals in a
所以通常当一个
collection I look at that and say you
我看着那个说你
know if you if you if you look beyond
知道如果你，如果你如果你超越
that there's probably a better way to
可能有更好的方法
represent that in your application and
在您的应用程序中表示
optional kind of doesn't buy you
可选的种类不会买你
anything there so anyway rule six avoid
那里有什么，所以反正则六避免
using optional and field method
使用可选和现场方法
parameters and collections all right a
参数和集合都可以吧
little bit more on fields here so
这里的田地多一点
optional is a box so we have like the
可选的是一个盒子，所以我们喜欢
Box primitives like Capitol integer and
框原始图元，例如Capitol integer和
capital double and and and so forth so
资本双倍等等
those are objects as compared to
那些是与
primitives which are very cheap so an
很便宜的原语
optional is a box around a reference and
可选的是引用周围的方框，
so it's a lot more expensive than a
所以它比
reference and so you can if you overuse
参考，所以如果您过度使用就可以
optional particularly if you use
可选，特别是如果您使用
optionals in collections or in field
集合或字段中的可选
then you can without realizing it
那你就可以不用意识到
greatly increase the amount of memory
大大增加内存量
your application consumes and have
您的应用程序消耗并拥有
caused GC to cur a lot more often so
导致GC经常更频繁地固化
forth also if you want to get the value
如果您想获得价值，也可以
out of an optional you have to do a
出于可选，您必须执行
dependent load so if you have a
依赖负载，所以如果您有
reference
参考
dereferencing it directly you have an
直接取消引用您有
optional that contains a reference so
可选，其中包含参考，因此
you have to make one hop into the
你必须跳一跳
optional and then another hop to to get
可选，然后再跳到另一个
to the actual object and so if you have
到实际对象，所以如果你有
a lot of those things if you have one of
很多这些东西，如果你有一个
them big deal but if you have a mil any
他们大不了，但如果你有百万
of them in a collection and you want to
他们在一个集合中，你想
reverse them you've probably created a
扭转他们，你可能已经创建了一个
million extra cache misses and that
一百万个额外的缓存未命中
really is going to slow down your
真的会减慢你的速度
program so so if you use optional very
程序，所以如果您使用非常可选
frequently or in data structures that is
经常或在数据结构中
probably a thing to avoid and I think
可能要避免的事情，我认为
what leads people into this oh I can use
是什么导致人们进入这个哦，我可以使用
optional in all these different places
在所有这些不同地方都是可选的
is that people think that optional is a
人们认为可选是
replacement for null and they go around
替换为null，他们四处走动
their code saying everywhere I'm going
他们的代码说我要去的任何地方
to use null I can replace it with
使用null我可以将其替换为
optional and that's not true optional is
可选的，这不是真的。
not intended as a replacement for a null
不打算替代null
reference again optional is narrowly
再次引用可选范围狭窄
focused on the problem of a return type
专注于返回类型的问题
that might or might not have value all
可能有或没有全部价值
right now I'll get into a little bit of
现在，我会讲一点
the history about the bike shedding in
关于自行车脱落的历史
the open JDK mailing lists where
打开的JDK邮件列表，其中
optional was discussed as in the design
在设计中讨论了可选
of JDK 8 there were an enormous number
JDK 8的数量众多
of emails about these they went hundreds
关于这些的电子邮件，他们去了数百
and hundreds and hundreds of emails that
以及成百上千的电子邮件
we called these sent to thread and they
我们称这些发送到线程，他们
raised a lot of issues and for something
提出了很多问题
you know which is conceptually so simple
你知道哪个在概念上如此简单
optional can need to be present or
可选的可能需要存在或
absent there are a remarkable number of
缺席的
different design decisions you can make
您可以做出不同的设计决策
so all of these questions were asked at
所以所有这些问题都在
some point or another the idea of bike
自行车的某些观点
shading came in which is okay so we make
可以进入阴影，所以我们
design decisions about how we're going
关于我们前进的设计决策
to design a class and somebody says oh
设计一堂课，有人说哦
no you shouldn't do it that way you
不，你不应该那样做
should do it this way instead and over
应该这样做，而不是结束
and over and over so the fact is in JDK
一遍又一遍，事实是在JDK中
8 we ended up with optional that has a
8我们最终得到了一个可选的
particular design particular design
特殊设计特殊设计
decisions and unfortunately those
决定，不幸的是
decisions are not to everybody's liking
决定不是每个人都喜欢
and there are some things we can do we
我们可以做一些事情
can fix it by adding some methods we can
可以通过添加一些方法来修复它
maybe deprecated get that might improve
也许过时的获取可能会改善
things but there are some things that
东西，但是有些东西
you know that are not going to be the
你知道那不会是
people's liking and so I'm going to talk
人们喜欢，所以我要谈谈
about a couple of them here one of them
大约有几个，其中一个
is optional is not serializable and this
是可选的，不可序列化，这
so in jdk eight the java.util optional
因此在jdk中有八个java.util可选
class is not serializable and this is
类不可序列化，这是
particularly irksome to people who are
对于那些特别讨厌的人
using lavas optional in fact the the
使用熔岩可选事实上
project lead of guava was on the expert
番石榴项目负责人是专家
group for Java 8 so in fact the Java 8
Java 8组，因此实际上是Java 8
optional was descended from guavas
可选是番石榴的后代
optional so there's a lot of the same
可选的，所以有很多相同的地方
thinking going on there
想去那里
however lava is optional is serializable
但是熔岩是可选的，可以序列化
whereas the JDK S is not and the reason
而JDK S不是，原因是
for that is I'm going to have to
因为那是我将不得不
compress this pretty highly but we have
高度压缩，但是我们有
this thing that we've been working on a
这个我们一直在努力的东西
pipe called project Valhalla where we
管道称为Valhalla项目
want to introduce the notion of value
想要介绍价值的概念
types value types do not have any
类型值类型没有任何值
identity and if you look at
身份，如果你看
serialization in any detail you realize
您意识到的任何细节的序列化
that it is tightly bound into the notion
它与概念紧密相关
of serialized things being objects and
序列化的东西是对象，
when you see realized something and
当你看到意识到的东西，
deserialize it you get an object back
反序列化它会得到一个对象
and an object inescapably has identity
一个对象不可避免地具有身份
and in project Valhalla we want to have
在Valhalla项目中，我们希望拥有
values that do not have identity and so
没有身份等的价值观
making optional serializable will
使可选的可序列化的遗嘱
preclude us from turning optional into a
阻止我们将可选变成
value type in the future so that's what
未来的价值类型就是这样
we're that's our thinking on this but
这就是我们的想法，但是
mainly and so you can see this in the
主要，因此您可以在
disclaimer in the Javadoc if you
Javadoc中的免责声明，如果您
actually go look in Java 8 it says that
实际去看Java 8它说
has this word but basically the rule is
有这个词，但基本上是
avoid using identity sensitive
避免使用身份敏感
operations on optionals and so basically
可选操作等等
don't use reference equality with
不要使用引用相等
optional alright so here is here's a
可选，好的，这是一个
little more probably too much detail on
可能更多的细节
serialization I'm not going to go
序列化我不会去
through this I'll post the slides later
通过这个我以后再发布幻灯片
you can look through this in detail but
您可以详细浏览一下，但是
this basically says when you do but when
这基本上是在说什么时候
you deal with serialization this binds
你处理序列化绑定
you firmly into the object space and
您坚定地进入对象空间，
everything in the object base has
对象库中的所有内容都具有
identity all right why not use optional
身份好吧，为什么不使用可选
and field so I talked about this
和田野，所以我谈到了
somewhat before I think this is a style
在我认为这是一种风格之前
issue some people would like to do that
有些人想这样做
and if it makes sense for your
如果这对您有意义
application and it performs well and
应用程序，它表现良好，并且
it's not a problem I guess that's okay
这不是问题，我想那没关系
I'm not going to tell you you're wrong
我不会告诉你你错了
if you want to use optional infield but
如果您想使用可选的内场但是
it kind of tells me that there might be
有点告诉我可能有
something else going on as we already
我们已经发生了其他事情
talked about the memory overhead and
谈到内存开销，
again this idea that I think some people
再次这个想法，我认为有些人
want to avoid using nulls at all cost
想要不惜一切代价避免使用null
and so well you know I think that's
所以很好，你知道我认为那是
trade-off that you have to make if you
如果您必须进行权衡
want to avoid nulls by creating optional
想要通过创建可选值来避免空值
objects everywhere and doing extra
到处都是对象，并做额外的工作
pointer dereferences using extra memory
指针使用额外的内存取消引用
and probably even cluttering up your
甚至会弄乱你的
code tomorrow you know I think the
代码明天你知道我认为
trade-off that you can make if you want
您可以根据需要进行权衡
to but it's not it's not a choice that I
，但这不是我的选择
would make myself personally yeah and so
会让自己成为个人等等
there's some discussion on this on the
关于这个有一些讨论
on the internet there are a couple
互联网上有几个
people who are quite vocal about this
对此大声疾呼的人
steven kolb ORN wrote a blog article
史蒂文·科尔布（Steven Kolb）ORN写了一篇博客文章
called optional a pragmatic approach and
称为可选的实用方法
he goes through a number of a number of
他经历了许多
scenarios we have some generally good
我们总体上有一些好的情况
advice on fields his recommendation is
关于领域的建议，他的建议是
if you have a field that might or might
如果您的字段可能或可能
not contain a value just use a knowable
不包含值，只是使用一个已知的
reference and in your API if you want to
参考和在您的API中，如果您想
return an optional at the point where
在以下位置返回可选
you return it is where you create the
您返回的位置就是您创建
optional I think that's a very
可选，我认为这是一个非常
interesting approach it's a pragmatic
有趣的方法，这是实用的
approach as he put it but I think
他所说的方法，但我认为
actually one thing I did forget to
实际上我忘了一件事
mention which which that point brings up
提到那一点提到哪一点
is think about your internal
想着你的内部
representation differently from your API
表示形式与您的API不同
the optional construct is an API
可选结构是API
constructs it's useful for API return
构造它对于API返回很有用
values but that doesn't mean you have to
值，但这并不意味着您必须
use optional in your internal
在内部使用可选
representation so Stephen has a good
代表，所以斯蒂芬有一个很好的
example he says use null inside optional
他说的示例在可选内部使用null
outside I think that's good advice so
在外面，我认为这是个好建议
another another reference I have here is
我在这里的另一个参考是
to an article by my current who is here
到我现在在这里的一篇文章
at this conference he's giving a talk on
在这次会议上，他正在演讲
his checkers framework earlier and so
他的跳棋框架更早，等等
here's a link to that article and in the
这是该文章的链接，在
checkers framework he has what he calls
他有他所说的跳棋框架
an ulness checker and so if you have the
ulness检查器，所以如果您有
idea that you want to get rid of nulls
您想摆脱空值的想法
throughout your code you should probably
在整个代码中，您可能应该
take a look at this
看看这个
because as I said as I said before
因为正如我之前所说
optional is not going to get rid of all
可选不会摆脱所有
nulls in your program it only is focused
在您的程序中为null，它仅被关注
on a certain portion of the use cases so
在用例的某些部分上
here I say the glass is one-quarter full
在这里我说杯子装满了四分之一
right so optional is very useful for
对，所以可选对
return types but it's not useful for
返回类型，但对
optional method parameters not useful
可选方法参数无用
for fields not useful for this that in
对于对此没有用的字段
the other right so okay I think so the
另一个权利好吧，我想是
glass is one-quarter full for optional
玻璃为四分之一装满（可选）
it's really useful for return types but
这对于返回类型非常有用，但是
you know it's useful for that use it for
你知道它对于将它用于
that all right so that brings me to the
没关系，这样就把我带到了
summary and conclusion here again a
总结和结论再次在这里
restatement of the design goals of
重述设计目标
optional a limited mechanism for return
可选的有限回报机制
types where there's a clean clear need
有明确需求的类型
to represent no result and where null is
表示没有结果，其中null为
likely to cause errors all right and
可能会导致错误，并且
then here the seven rules that I went
然后是我遵循的七个规则
through during the beginning I'll leave
在开始的时候我会离开
these up for a while if you want to take
这些，如果你想拿一会儿
a look at that and looks like I have a
看看那个，看起来我有一个
few minutes for questions so if you have
几分钟提问，如果有的话
questions they're mics at the front of
他们是前面的麦克风的问题
the aisles here the front of the room
房间前面的过道
there any questions
有什么问题
quick question um to share some of the
快速问题，以分享一些
possible names for the replacement of
替换的可能名称
debt ah where did you have any yet no I
债务啊，你在哪里还没有我
I think naming okay so the naming is
我认为命名可以，所以命名是
hard I think I did have a replacement
很难，我认为我确实有一个替代者
which I don't want to say because then
我不想说因为
we'll just react to it I propose the
我们会对此做出回应，我建议
replacement people reacted the
替代人反应了
replacement and then that that caused
更换，然后导致
another by trading argument to spin off
通过交易分拆另一个
but if people have suggestions well
但是如果人们有好的建议
maybe I shouldn't say this but if people
也许我不应该这样说，但是如果人们
have suggested tweet him to me
建议给我发推文
oh actually I forgot to mention I'll get
哦，实际上我忘了提我会得到
to you in a moment sir
先生，给你
in the upper right corner of the slides
在幻灯片的右上角
there's a hashtag if you want to talk
如果你想说话有一个标签
about this on Twitter I'm on Twitter you
关于这个在推特上我在推特上
can tweet to me on that hashtag I'll
可以在标签上向我发送推文
look forward after the conference or you
期待会议结束后还是你
can tweet to me directly
可以直接发给我
so yeah question we eventually get
是的，我们最终会得到问题
India's empty method if you and key
印度的空方法，如果您和密钥
method for optional oh that's a good
可选方法不错
that's a good point because sometimes
这是一个好点，因为有时
it's inconvenient to test for not is
测试不方便是
present I think that's the main thing so
目前，我认为这是主要问题
it's a little bit of kind of API
这有点像API
syntactic sugar I think you know maybe I
句法糖我想你知道也许我
think the thing is if you you know we
认为事情是如果你知道我们
need to be bunch of use cases where if
需要一堆用例，如果
it's over and over and over this is
一遍又一遍，这是
causing a lot of clutter maybe we could
造成很多混乱，也许我们可以
add it but generally it doesn't it
添加它，但通常不是
doesn't add anything fundamental that
没有添加任何基本内容
you couldn't do using you know not is
你不能使用，你知道不是
present so maybe I know there are other
目前，所以也许我知道还有其他
places in the API where we do have it I
我确实在API中放置的位置
think we have object shot is null and
认为我们拍摄的物体为空并且
object non doll or something like that
非玩偶之类的东西
and those are really useful for method
这些对于方法真的很有用
references so I mean that's a
引用，所以我的意思是
possibility but it's kind of it's not
可能性，但不是
not the not the most important thing at
不是不是最重要的事情
the moment question so my question is
当下的问题，所以我的问题是
regarding rule number two if you can
关于第二条规则，如果可以的话
prove that the value can be no why would
证明价值可以不是为什么
you even use optional oh okay well so
你甚至可以使用可选的哦，好吧，所以
the again if you think about how
再一次，如果您考虑如何
optional is used you're calling some
可选用的是你在打电话
method somewhere else and it returns you
其他地方的方法，它会返回您
an optional and so what that method is
可选的，那是什么方法
telling you is there might or might not
告诉你那里可能有也可能没有
be a value present now
成为现在的价值
one way to prove that a values present
一种证明存在价值的方法
is to call is present on it and check
是要呼叫存在并检查
the return value but there are other
返回值，但还有其他
cases where like in the streams API it's
在流API中的情况
a little too complicated for me to hand
我手太复杂了
wave and I don't have the I don't have
挥手，我没有，我没有
the code handy but there cases where in
方便的代码，但在某些情况下
the streams API some of the methods
流API的一些方法
return an optional of something but if
返回一个可选的东西，但是如果
you set up your data structures in a
您在一个
particular way and you are absolutely
特殊的方式，你绝对
certain that that optional can contain a
确定该可选内容可以包含一个
value and there's no way it can be empty
值，它不可能为空
then go ahead and call get on it but
然后继续打电话给它，但是
what you have to do is you have to make
你要做的就是要做
a global assertion about your data
关于数据的全局断言
structures in the state of your program
程序状态下的结构
before you can do that and so sometimes
在您可以做到之前，有时
it's straightforward is calling gap but
直截了当地说差距
sometimes it's a global assertion about
有时这是关于
your program so that make sense well
您的程序，这样很好
maybe we can talk about it after all
毕竟我们可以谈谈
coming up with a simple example or
提出一个简单的例子或
something thank you okay well Java ever
好的，谢谢你，Java
get a safe traversal operator base and
获得安全的遍历运算符基础，并
if we're chaining things together
如果我们将事物链接在一起
oh love the Elvis operator ah yes the
哦，爱猫王操作员啊，是的
Elvis operator um probably not I think
猫王运算符嗯，我可能不是
there were some attempts to do that in
有一些尝试这样做
project coin in Java 7 and there was
Java 7中的项目硬币
some effort put into them and they I
他们付出了一些努力，他们我
don't you know it's always hard to hard
你不知道总是很难吗
to say why something didn't succeed I
说为什么有些事情没有成功
think this is one where somebody said
认为这是有人说的
all this Adobe ought to be really easy
所有这些Adobe应该真的很容易
they prototyped it turned out to be
他们原型证明它是
really hard which is which is not at all
真的很难，这根本不是
uncommon when you're changing the
更改时不常见
programming language I think though the
我认为虽然编程语言
I think there's this philosophy this is
我认为这是一种哲学
kind of a philosophical point is as time
一种哲学观点是时间
goes on we are trying to gravitate away
继续，我们正在努力吸引
from away from things that tolerate null
远离容忍null的事物
so for instance that the Java 9
例如Java 9
collected immutable collections that
收集了不可变的集合
that I introduced I'll be talking about
我介绍的我将要谈论
this in my session tomorrow
明天在我的会议上
those are null hostile if you attempt to
如果您尝试
put a null in one of those they throw a
在其中一个扔一个空值
null pointer exception and
空指针异常和
kind of kind of the same with optional
与可选相同
dot of you try to put a null reference
您试图将一个空引用
into that it throws an exception and so
引发异常，因此
what we're trying to do is say okay
我们想做的是说好
we know there are a lot of nulls out
我们知道有很多空值
there we want to avoid using them and so
在那里我们要避免使用它们，所以
within the boundary have you know have
在边界内你知道吗
safe code that doesn't doesn't deal with
不处理的安全代码
nulls because and doesn't have to deal
空值，因为并且不必处理
with nulls and I think the thing about
用空值，我想关于
the null safe traversal or the Elvis
空安全遍历或猫王
operator is what it does is it
操作员是做什么的
encourages nulls to spread all over and
鼓励零星散布到各处
every time you write that then it's like
每次你写的时候就像
oh well what if it's no now I don't care
哦，好吧，如果现在不行，我不在乎
I'll just use this operator and nulls
我将使用此运算符和null
propagate everywhere until you get to a
传播到任何地方，直到你到达
point where you cannot deal with them
指出你无法应付的地方
and and and then you're hosed so I think
然后你被用软管吸住，所以我想
I I don't think there's any there's any
我不认为有任何东西
impetus to adding null safe traversal at
推动在以下位置添加空安全遍历
this point any further questions okay
这一点还有其他问题吗
that looks like it thanks for coming
看起来像谢谢你的光临
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]